CONTACT Information Removed for online version.

Phone: Removed for online version. Email: clay.l.mcleod@gmail.com Webpaqe: claymcleod.github.io

RESEARCH Interests Applying practical machine learning techniques to generate actionable business insights. Currently focusing on deep learning, bayesian statistics, and quantative analytics.

EDUCATION

University of Mississippi, University, MS

M. S. Computer Science

May 2016

- Major GPA 4.0/4.0, Overall GPA 3.88/4.0
- Financed my college education through assistantships and scholarships.

B. S. Electrical Engineering (emphasis in Computer Engineering)

May 2014

- Major GPA 3.81/4.0, Overall GPA 3.66/4.0
- Graduate of the Sally McDonald Barksdale Honors College

Professional Experience

CM Technology, LLC - Memphis, TN

Co-Founder and Vice President

January 2015 - Present

- Sole electrical and software engineer for a company focused on providing technological innovation to the construction industry.
- Complete native mobile app on iPhone (Swift), website and server written on the MEAN stack (MongoDB, ExpressJS, AngularJS, NodeJS).
- Created proprietary microelectronic device to compliment software solution.

FedEx Services - Memphis, TN

Software Analyst Intern

Summer 2015

- Built a native, internal mobile application for iOS (Swift) and Android (Java).
- Created a scalable backend server with NodeJS, ExpressJS, and MongoDB.
- Created a proprietary machine learning server/path optimization server written in Python with open-source tools such as scikit-learn and pandas.
- Recipient of the FedEx Technical Mastery award (x2) and the Director's Choice Award for best project. Employee choice award for 2015 best intern project.

University of Mississippi - University, MS

Head Teacher's Assistant

Fall 2014 - Present

- Full time assistantship that financed Master's degree.
- Hired and managed 30 teacher's assistants. Coordinated lab times programming classes.
- Managed 400 student's lab grades throughout the year.

Research Assistant (Biometric security)

October 2013 - Present

- Developed a new kind of biometric authentication system for mobile security using machine learning, exponentially decreasing the likelihood of a successful attack on the system.
- Currently pursuing patent for this software.

Research Assistant (Facial Recognition)

Spring 2011 - Fall 2012

- Researched and wrote platform independent facial recognition software.
- Skills learned include proficiency in the C and JavaScript languages, knowledge of the WebGL pipeline, and specialized implementation of the OpenGL Shading Language.

Logical Systems, LLC. - Memphis, TN

Electrical Engineering Intern

Summer 2014

- Fabricated multiple electrical control panels for a wide range of applications.
- Assisted engineers with control automation design in AutoCAD.

Relevant Skills

Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Data Mining, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, AngularJS, SocketIO Redis, Python, R, Data Science, Web Design, Java, Javascript, Project Management, Docker, CoreOS.